# Paulo Bezerra

## Support Analyst PL at EY

pauloh2012sul@gmail.com

# Summary

Experienced Support Analyst with a demonstrated history of working in the accounting industry. Skilled in Windows, Java programming, OS X, Operations Management, Microsoft Excel, IT Service Management, VBA, SQL, ETL, Dashboards creation and Systems Implementation. Strong information technology professional with a Bachelor's Degree focused in Computer Systems Analysis from Senac São Paulo.

# Experience

### **Support Analyst at EY**

June 2014 - Present

- Solid knowledge in Microsoft Excel, VBA, ETL and Performance Indicators.
- Responsible for create and maintain the operational KPIs reports generated daily and presented to the lead using his automatic templates.
- Paulo created internal tools developed in Java to decrease the call time during the Support.
- Provide remote assistance (Phone, Chat and Email) mainly to EY Brazil internal and external
- customers, performed in Portuguese and English languages;
- Troubleshooting problems related to internal software, operating systems, email
- applications, office tools, network connectivity and telephony;
- Tickets escalation for several global teams using ITIL methodology;
- Participation in projects to improve processes in Service Desk area, automatizing internal process, working together with other teams to minimize the impact of new deployments.

#### Service Desk Analyst at Nestle S.A.

October 2013 - May 2014 (8 months)

Paulo worked as Bilingual Remote Support Analyst in MS Windows Vista and Windows 7 platforms. He provided support in systems as AS400, SAP(Module FI and CO), Checkpoint, Active Directory, BitLocker, Mercury and other applications using the HP Service Manager;

#### **Deployment Analyst at Flash Courier**

November 2008 - October 2013 (5 years)

Paulo worked for five years as Implementation Analyst, System Tester and Project Manager in a logistic company. His main roles were create Project Scopes and Algorithms for new clients and new tools, defining metrics and layouts, creating internal and external SLA's reports models with customers, partners and vendors, participate in the Business decisions as IT member consultant, analysing and creating reports and assisting from the beginning of new projects until the deployment.

## **Administrative Assistant at Deloitte**

October 2006 - July 2008 (1 year 10 months)

Paulo started his career as Administrative Assistant trainee at Deloitte when he was 16. He worked for about two years assisting in administrative routines in audit firm's office.

# Education

## Senac São Paulo

Bachelor's Degree, Computer Systems Analysis, 2017 - 2019

# Paulo Bezerra

Support Analyst PL at EY

pauloh2012sul@gmail.com



Contact Paulo on LinkedIn